chooseyouritem.com 2019-02-27

# Online vehicle classifieds with photos. For sale classifieds. Sell it with pictures.

  | 

## Use Agreement and Privacy Statement

ChooseYourItem.com is designed to serve buyers and sellers of property for sale. While every effort is made to be accurate, by using this site or any ChooseYourItem.com services, you agree that neither the advertisers nor the publisher will be responsible for misinformation, typographical errors, etc., herein or for any form of damages arising from the viewing of, the use of, or participation in any of the related websites or services. You are agreeing that viewing and usage of the same is at your own risk. Company names, manufacturer names and model names of the items listed as well as logos are the property of their respective companies and are used only for purposes of identifying the element. No part of ChooseYourItem.com or its published material may be reproduced in any form without prior consent of the publisher. 

## Our Privacy Policy

ChooseYourItem.com is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. The following outlines our information gathering, use and dissemination practices for the Choseyouritem.com website.

## Consumer Information

As you view our website, ChooseYourItem.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address unless you choose to provide us with such information. For example, you may voluntarily provide personal identifiable information when you place a vehicle for sale on our website.

ChooseYourItem.com does automatically collect some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider, domain name or IP address you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by ChooseYourItem.com is used for the purpose of measuring the effectiveness of our web site.

ChooseYourItem.com may aggregate information collected on this website in order to understand more about who visits this website. None of the aggregated information is used to identify anyone personally.

When certain types of personal information (such as credit card information) are requested, we redirect you through a secure server (You should see the padlock in your browser signifying that the page is using SSL. If this is not the case, please do not enter personal information and contact us immediately). This information is saved in an encrypted format and then is transferred and stored encrypted off the Internet (for example, on CD-ROM or DVD).

Of course, information that is voluntarily presented as contact information for a "for sale" listing will be publicly displayed on our web site.

Information we collect may be disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website. This information may be disclosed to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, or other corporate change respecting the website.

We may use cookies to store search keywords or other information that will better serve visitors when they return to our website (for example, we may automatically fill in previous search keywords into our search fields so you don't have to retype keywords each time).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information about your visits to this website in order to tailor advertisements on this website, other sites and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp)

If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.

If you are participating in any form of newsletter program that is being managed and hosted by ChooseYourItem.com, the email address that you provide to us will only be used by ChooseYourItem.com to send email communications that you have specifically told us you are interested in receiving. This information will never be made available to any third parties. You may remove yourself from the newsletter program at any time by contacting us using the "Contact Us" link below. 

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

|
